<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Myself on Charles Mclean</title><link>https://blog.whitecat.dev/tags/myself/</link><description>Recent content in Myself on Charles Mclean</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.whitecat.dev/tags/myself/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My Future</title><link>https://blog.whitecat.dev/p/future/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.whitecat.dev/p/future/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="my-future">My future
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>I hope to further enhance my cybersec skills, especially at the university I will be attending, in which I aspire to become the best hacking version of myself. I will pursue my self-taught adventures and projects before I attend this university, just like the fully local and containerised ai i have been working on. Here is a link to the project: (use the &lt;em>showcase&lt;/em> user with the &lt;em>showcase&lt;/em> password)
&lt;a class="link" href="https://blog.whitecat.dev/p/ai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>WhiteCat&amp;rsquo;s Local AI&lt;/a> My next certification in my sights is the OSCP (aka PEN-200) from OffSec. This certification, although seen as a less complete version of CPTS, is the most recognizable and known pentesting certification on the market. I will continue to attend the CTFs in my area and hope to get the highest score I can achieve.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Now, enough talked about myself, lets get to tutorials and knowledge on hacking all kinds of stuff!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My Past Experiences</title><link>https://blog.whitecat.dev/p/past/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.whitecat.dev/p/past/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="my-past">My past
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>I have always been a geek in terms of computers and IT. When it came to making Minecraft servers at the age of 11 years old or just goofing around in Kali Linux when I was young, having no idea what I was doing, I started my interest in computers at a young age. At the age of 14, I started playing around with servers and virtualization - I notably built my own homelab based (at the time) on UnRaid.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I next went on my Nova PC endeavor at the age of 15 years old. This company first started out as a &amp;ldquo;Custom PC Building&amp;rdquo; service where you could choose every part of your PC online and we would build it for you. This website was mainly built on WordPress and would later on be switched over to a native and static Next.js website for speed and optimization.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>See more:
&lt;a class="link" href="https://blog.whitecat.dev/p/nova-pc/" >Nova PC&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We started out, as a team of three, the PlayStranded Modded Rust Server. This custom but mostly QoL improvements on the base game of Rust offered multiple game servers, all hosted in my basement. After which we had to shut down the server due to lack of time spent for advertising and other concerns such as school. After the shutdown of PlayStranded, we switched back to reviving the Nova PC business image. This implied a complete makeover, such as switching to web hosting and game hosting.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Later came the time to choose which of my CEGEP studies I would be undertaking - cybersec and networking was an obvious choice. In the meantime, I completed the CPTS certification from HackTheBox, which was an incredible and enriching experience. I now no longer operate any companies but do some work on the side other than the technical support team at school.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>